http://pelvicpartnership.org.uk/privacy-policy/

Shop: our publications
What is PGP?
Pain in PGP
Acute or chronic pain?
Elective caesarean section
Twins (and more)
Pelvic floor and PGP
Coccyx pain (coccydynia)
PGP following pregnancy
Future pregnancies and periods
Responded to treatment but not 100%
Understanding chronic (persistent) pelvic pain
If it's not PGP, then what could it be?
Shop: our publications
What is PGP?
Pain in PGP
Acute or chronic pain?
Elective caesarean section
Twins (and more)
Pelvic floor and PGP
Coccyx pain (coccydynia)
PGP following pregnancy
Future pregnancies and periods
Responded to treatment but not 100%
Understanding chronic (persistent) pelvic pain
If it's not PGP, then what could it be?
Our members' area
At The Pelvic Partnership, we’re committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.
This Policy explains when and why we collect personal information about people who visit our website, how we use it, the conditions under which we may disclose it to others and how we keep it secure.
We may change this Policy from time to time so please check this page occasionally to ensure that you’re happy with any changes. By using our website, you’re agreeing to be bound by this Policy.
Any questions regarding this Policy and our privacy practices should be sent by email to contact@pelvicpartnership.org.uk or by writing to The Pelvic Partnership, 16 The Cleave, Harwell, Oxon, OX11 0EL.
Who are the Pelvic Partnership?
We’re a small charity registered in England (no.1100373) which operates nationally. We support and provide information to women with pregnancy-related Pelvic Girdle Pain (PGP) and their families and carers. We also provide information to healthcare professionals involved in the care of women with PGP. Our registered address is 16 The Cleave, Harwell, Oxon, OX11 0EL.
How do we collect information from you?
We obtain information about you when you use our website, for example, when you order an information pack, join as a member or make a donation.
What type of information is collected from you?
The personal information we collect might include your name, address, telephone number, email address, IP address, and information regarding what pages are accessed and when. If you join as a member, make a donation online or purchase a publication from us, your card information is not held by us, it is collected by PayPal payment processors, who specialise in the secure online capture and processing of credit/debit card transactions, as explained below.
How is your information used?
We may use your information to:
process a donation that you have made;
process orders that you have submitted;
to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into by you and us for example membership;
seek your views or comments on the information we provide;
notify you of changes to our services;
send you communications which you have requested and that may be of interest to you. These may include information about campaigns, conferences, fundraising opportunities or surveys.
We are legally required to hold some types of information to fulfill our statutory obligations (for example the collection of Gift Aid). We will hold your personal information on our secure systems for as long as is necessary for the relevant activity, or as long as is set out in any relevant contract you hold with us.
Who has access to your information?
We will not sell or rent your information to third parties.We will not share your information with third parties for marketing purposes.
When you are using our secure online donation or payment pages, your donation, membership or publication payment is processed by PayPal, who specialise in the secure online capture and processing of credit/debit card transactions. Please refer to PayPal’s privacy policy If you have any questions regarding secure transactions, please contact us.
Your choices
You have a choice about whether or not you wish to receive information from us. If you do not want to receive communications from us about the work we do for women with PGP including our publications and other products, campaigns, fundraising opportunities and surveys, then you can select your choices by ticking the relevant boxes situated on the form on which we collect your information.
We will not contact you by email, post or phone if you have indicated that you do not wish to be contacted. You can change your preferences at any time by contacting us by email: contact@pelvicpartnership.org.uk or by clicking ‘unsubscribe’ at the bottom of any email we send to you.
How you can access and update your information
The accuracy of your information is important to us. If you change email address, or any of the other information we hold is inaccurate or out of date, please email us at: contact@pelvicpartnership.org.uk, or write to us at: 16 The Cleave, Harwell, Oxon, OX11 0EL.
You have the right to ask for a copy of the information the Pelvic Partnership hold about you. We may charge £5 for information requests to cover our administration costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.
Security precautions in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of your information
When you give us personal information, we take steps to ensure that it’s treated securely. Any sensitive information (such as credit or debit card details) is encrypted and protected by PayPal (please see their privacy policy). When you are on a secure page, a lock icon will appear on the bottom of web browsers such as Microsoft Internet Explorer.
Non-sensitive details (your email address etc.) are transmitted normally over the Internet, and this can never be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your information, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. Where we have given (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access our members’ area, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.
Profiling
We may analyse your personal information to create a profile of your interests and preferences so that we can contact you with information relevant to you. This information is kept confidential.
Use of ‘cookies’
Like many other websites, the Pelvic Partnership website uses cookies when our members’ login to our members’ only area. ‘Cookies’ are small pieces of information sent by an organisation to your computer and stored on your hard drive to allow that website to recognise you when you visit. They collect statistical data about your browsing actions and patterns and do not identify you as an individual.
Links to other websites
Our website contains links to other websites run by other organisations. This privacy policy applies only to our website‚ so we encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit. We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other sites even if you access them using links from our website.
In addition, if you linked to our website from a third party site, we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of the owners and operators of that third party site and recommend that you check the policy of that third party site.
16 or Under
We are concerned to protect the privacy of children aged 16 or under. If you are aged 16 or under‚ please get your parent/guardian’s permission beforehand whenever you provide us with personal information.
Website hosting and content back up
The content on our website and all membership, donation and shop order form data is backed up regularly and securely saved to Rochen Web Hosting. Please see Rochen’s privacy policy for further information about how they store data.
Review of this Policy
We keep this Policy under regular review. This Policy was last updated in April 2018.
About us
Contact us & FAQs
Blog
Privacy policy
Charity Registered in England: 1100373
The Pelvic Partnership consists of volunteers who have had pelvic girdle pain (PGP) and wish to support other women. We aim to pass on information based on both research and the experience of other women with PGP. We are not medical professionals and cannot offer medical advice and the information we provide should not take the place of advice and guidance from your own health-care providers. Material on this site is provided for information and support purposes only.   © Copyright Pelvic Partnership 2020
This website was built by Jigsaw Web Design Ltd
Username or Email Address
Password
Remember Me
Log In
Lost your password?
